In the adaptor bindView method, we have to traverse the view
hierarchy to find all these different views to set data onto
them. If it's a recycled view, meaning that it was used
in the list previously to display other data, we still have
to traverse and find all the views. To remove unnecessary find
View By ID calls, we can use the View Holder pattern.
For a list item layout that contains different views, we can
create a View Holder object. It contains member variables that reference each
view in the layout. The View Holder object is stored in
the tag field of the view. The next time that the view
is recycled and used again. We can just immediately set the data
onto these fields. You don't have to go find all the views
again. This is our View Holder class. You can name it anything
you want, it's just a Java class. Given the list item layout,
we do all the find view by ID calls. That way, we
can hold references to all the child views. In the newView method,
after we've inflated the view, we create a new View Holder object
from that view. Then we set the View Holder as the tag of
the view. The tag can be used to store any object. But
don't abuse it, because when you read it back, you have to know
what you stored in there. A View Holder is a good use
case for it. Then in the bindView method. We read from the tag,
to get back the View Holder object. And we immediately have references, to
all the individual views we need to update, such as the Icon View,
the Date View, the Description View etc. Go ahead and define a View
Holder class and update your adapter to use it. When you compile and
run, you may not see that noticeable of a difference. But now your
list will perform better when it scales to hundreds or thousands of items.